{
    "file_name": "Vocabulary",
    "list_questions": [
        {
            "id": 0,
            "question": "In winter accidents happen quite ... on the roads.",
            "options": [
                " frequently",
                " quietly",
                "frequent",
                "sometimes"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Although they are brother and sister, they ... speak to each other these days. ",
            "options": [
                " hardy ",
                " hardly ",
                " strictly ",
                " mainly"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "He goes to London every ... week.",
            "options": [
                " two",
                "another",
                "other",
                "both"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "He drives ....",
            "options": [
                " pretty fast",
                "nicely fast ",
                "quick ",
                "enough fast"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "At the meeting, the manager talked ... about the need for better attendance and punctuality.",
            "options": [
                "briefing ",
                "shortly ",
                "shorts ",
                "briefly"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "Hard work ... pays off.",
            "options": [
                "advertises ",
                "eventually ",
                "never ",
                "will sometimes"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "I guess he is ... 30.",
            "options": [
                "approximatively ",
                "approximately ",
                "more the less ",
                "an average of"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "With this beautiful blue sky, it is very ... to rain, isn\u2019t it?",
            "options": [
                "probable",
                "likely",
                "improbable",
                "unlikely"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "He has just lost his contact lens but it is ... be found. How very strange!",
            "options": [
                "somewhere",
                "anywhere",
                "nothing",
                "nowhere"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "Who said we were ... ?",
            "options": [
                "whole like",
                "all like",
                "all alike",
                "whole alike"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        }
    ]
}